# NATHANAEL GANDHI

#### MECHATRONIC ENGINEER



+61 431 905 747

nathanaelgandhi@gmail.com

New South Wales, Australia

MathanaelGandhi.com

## SKILLS

- Embedded Software (C/C++)
- Electronic Design Automation
- · Prototyping, Soldering
- Strong Communication
- Managing Client Relations
- Autonomous Team Member
- CI & Containerized Development
- · Linux Based Operating Systems

## **EDUCATION**

## BE(HONS) MECHATRONIC DipProfEngPrac

University of Technology Sydney 2017 - 2022

#### **DIPLOMA OF ENGINEERING**

UTS:Insearch

2016

2023 Australian Space Awards Graduate of the Year - Finalist

### PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional engineer with five years of experience in electronic systems design and development. Strong teamwork, research and development skills. Projects & blog posts available on my website. The best way to get to know me is for us to have a chat.

## EXPERIENCE

#### **AIT ENGINEER**

Space Machines Company

2021 - Present

- Developed flight software in C derived from NASA
- Low-level hardware interactions & unit testing
- Designed and assembled electronics for engineering and flight
- Tested and reviewed spacecraft electrical components & systems

#### **RESEARCH ASSISTANT**

Robotics Institute: University of Technology Sydney (F.K.A Centre for Autonomous Systems)

2018 - 2021

- Modeled and verified sensing technology using Matlab and ROS
- Built power conditioning and distribution PCBs & harnesses
- Mechanical lead for self-driving mobility platform

#### **EXECUTIVE**

Robotics Society: University of Technology Sydney 2018 - 2022

- 2020 2022 Treasurer | Events | Technical Advisor
- 2019 President
  - 24 events involving technical, industry and social aspects
  - Mentored 4 teams in interstate and local competitions
  - Hosted UTS information and experience tours